Streets
=======
This is a fork of webdesigner97's streets mod, with Ragnarok's infrastructure mod sort of duct-taped in there (for now - there are plans to have them slowly become one).

Interesting Links:
==================
Github:		https://github.com/cheapie/streets

License:
==================
CC-BY-SA 3.0 Unported:

You are free:
	• to share (to copy, ditribute and transmit the work)
	• to remix (to adapt the work)
	• to make commercial use of the work

Under the following conditions:
	• Attribution (You must attribute the work in the manner specified by the author or  licensor.
	• Share Alike (If you alter, transform, or build upon this work, you may distribute the resulting work only under the same or similar license to this one.)

► http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0

For more information, see license.txt
